In this demo, the instrumental part
is simulated with Max/MSP
We can control the tempo (speed)
of the simulation
Now, let's start the ReactiveML
Top-Level inside emacs.
First, we load the score played
by the musician
Then we create and run the
live-coding environment
Now, let us define the bass line
of the song
We start with a simple accompaniment,
only the bass
We control the bass with a signal
kill_bass
The accompaniment follows the tempo
Now, we can try another style
for the accompaniment
Not bad, but it does not feel right...
Let's try another one.
That's the one!
Finally we can dynamically switch
between accompaniment styles
Let us start with the basic one
Then the waltz,
the arpeggio...
... and back to the basic one